group chat.
You can use one of those links.
Good job, Mr. Clark.
All right. All right. So, now let's do a
VM instance.
All right. So, now that we're VM
instances,
you can either go here or here. Same
thing.
That's pretty bright, Mr. Jackson.
Good job, Estress.
Good job, Mr. Jackson. All right.
So now we could go here create is this
from
instance templates.
I will go with this one.
That's the keys. Good job.
Did you do Hold on. Did you do SSH
test out SSH first?
When SSH
authorized
And this
>> good job. I like that
>> and just try that command line.
>> Good. Wow, look at you.
Oh, okay. Go and close that. Go close
SSH.
The SSH window. Go ahead and close it.
You don't. You did it. You tested it.
>> And now
open the Oh, open the browser.
Sorry. Go to the browser. Oh, there it
is. Good. Very good. I like this. You
did a great job.
>> Thank you.
>> Right. Um, put the proper link,
clickable link into the chat so we can
click on it.
>> Uh, Everett has a question for you. Go
ahead, Everett. Go and ask.
>> All right. I was just curious. Do you
need to use the same uh user script for
both the template and the instance?
>> What? Why are you asking that question?
Well, just what just so I know what to
grab because I was I was just curious if
you I I could easily just use use both
use it use the same, but I wouldn't know
if I had to because I'm I'm I hadn't
really done a template.
>> What I'm what I'm going into is your
process of thought here. This is what
I'm really emphasizing.
>> Yeah.
>> What we're showing you with a template
is how to deploy in an automated
fashion.
Your question requires
manual plus automated which would be
illogical.
There's no reason to do that.
>> I'm not I'm not let me let you know I'm
not following you first. This is the
first time I've heard of a template. Let
me So in other words, I have
>> this is why I'm teaching in the class
today templates because for all the
class this is templates the first time,
>> right? Okay. So for me to
>> everybody's in the same book.
>> Okay. So what I'm saying is I don't
really know what the purpose is. I'm
just following instructions. And so
>> good
>> when So when but when but but to to
speed up to what you just said. You said
my my process will require manual. I'm
not following that. I don't know what
you're what you're
>> process to require manual and automated.
Your original question is are you using
the um the startup script in both the
template and putting it in there?
Basically, it's it your the question is
illogical from the beginning. Why would
you need twice?
>> All right. So, for creating the VM
instance, you don't need to put Is it
what you're saying? Because I thought I
heard him say, but maybe I misheard it
or I didn't, but I thought I heard him
say that you had to grab the script and
put it in when you're creating the
instance, but he that's not true. We're
not putting that in for the instance,
only for the template. Is that what
you're saying?
>> Hold on. I'm gonna Guys, I want you guys
to teach him the process right now.
Everett, share your screen.
And Sean, you did a good job. Go ahead
and put your screen down.
>> One second. I have to uh bring this get
this out of the way here.
>> Yeah.
>> One second.
>> Let me see if I could.
>> Yeah. So essentially when he was
by the time I realized that he was
actually had moved into the instance I I
wasn't you know I was doing something
else and then so I was in the middle so
I didn't hear his whole instruction for
the instance. It's pretty that's all but
I'm trying to get back to the uh right
thing to there we go. Okay.
All right. So yeah I think replace
current. Okay. I'm going to click uh
send request or replace current share.
Let's see. You can request multiple
present
probably. Okay, let's try that.
>> Mr. Grant, bring your screen down.
>> Yep.
>> Is it uh Can you see my screen?
>> Okay. So, and we did not do anything in
this in this position here today.
>> In what POS? Well, let me let me bring
this over. Wait a minute. Which one do
you need to see? You probably need that,
I guess. Um,
so you know, I already did.
>> I got you remove your Visual Studio
Code. We're not doing anything with
Visual Studio Code. So, close that down.
>> I have so many screens open. Oh, you're
seeing You know what? I moved it to the
wrong monitor. Okay, this is this is the
right monitor for you, right? Let me uh
make that a little larger. So, yeah. So,
I created the template and I was about
to create the instance and my it was
just a
>> Hey, did he was Sean and Hold on. Was
Sean where you are today?
>> Was Shawn where I am today?
>> Yeah. Was did Shawn navigate to that
position today?
>> Well, what I'm saying is I He did this.
>> No, the answer is no. He did not.
>> Well, the answer I don't know. Yeah, I
don't know. I was I wasn't by the time
he started when he was talking about
creating the instance I didn't real cuz
he answered some other question and so I
was
>> okay so guys I want you to lead him
through doing this he has a he has a
template
>> now tell show him how to make an
instance from the template
>> okay go to you see VM instance
>> right yeah click on that And now create
instant.
Yeah. So you can give it a name if you
like.
>> Nope. Nope. Nope.
>> Wait.
>> What?
>> To create VM from.
>> Yeah. Okay. Wait. Yeah. Yeah. Create VM
form. Right up above.
Scroll. Yeah. Right there.
>> Yeah.
>> And then click on template.
>> Template. Yes.
>> Okay. Yeah, you're going to see it pop
up to the right side. Go all the way to
the right. Yeah, click on that.
>> Okay.
>> And
create.
Okay.
>> Yeah.
Okay. It's being generated.
>> Yep. Just wait.
All right.
So you see under connection connect you
see SSH under the instant you just
created. Yeah.
Authorize.
>> Good. Okay, that is good. Hold on. No,
you got to got to go in all the way.
Don't close that out. But this is good.
>> Yeah.
All right. So, it's taking longer than
usual, I think, to to establish a
connection. You want me to try it again?
>> Wait.
Yeah. Patience.
I wonder why. Oh yeah.
Okay.
So yeah, I will let's see. So
>> close that out.
>> Yeah, cuz when I created the template, I
did not create any kind of firewall. I
don't think I mean Okay, so uh let's
see.
Oh, let's see. Retri retry. I don't see
a close. Just to close it.
>> Yeah. X X
>> X. I don't see Do you see a
>> Yeah, right there. Yeah. Close. Close
this
window.
>> I got something blocking it. I think
it's the uh
>> Oh, well,
>> audio audio video. Let me see if I can
drag it down. No, I can't. D. Let's see
here. There we go. All right. Yeah.
>> All right.
That's strange.
Click on the external IP to see if it's
going to open like this.
Go. Okay. So, it worked.
>> Yeah, it worked.
Okay. Yeah, you can exit this.
>> Yep. You did it.
>> No, no. I mean, yeah, just the top
itself.
>> Yeah. See, I got this thing blocking so
much, man. Um, let me see. I don't know
how to get this out of the way. The
audio video participants and all that.
It's up there. Let me see more.
We can get this out off of my hide
panel.
No, that that's not it. Anyway, uh, all
right. I do it like this.
Then drag that down. Okay,
cool.
I wonder why SSH did not work for him.
>> Yeah. You want to go ahead and stop
sharing or keep sharing?
>> No, you did. You did the jump. That's
it.
>> Yeah. So, I'm going to stop sharing.
Okay. Thank you.
>> Okay. Who's next?
Who else wants to? Wait. Did everybody
do this?
Is there anybody who was unable to
deploy a VM from an instance?
Sorry. Anybody who was unable to deploy
a VM from an instance template.
And if you were able to deploy, did you
post your link? Did you post your your
link inside the chat?
You got a question, deal,
>> what's a question, Mike?
>> Hey, good afternoon. Um, so I've been
kind of behind on everything, so I
actually don't have the uh template
already pre-loaded when I was trying to
make the template. I know how to go Go
ahead.
that nobody has a template preloaded.
Everyone today started at the same
point.
>> Well, let me ask you this then.
something that go share your
>> guys teach him how to do this.
>> Somebody got this or
>> There we go. Okay,
guys. teach. Hold on for right now.
>> Knock down. Who's Who's sharing? This is
Michael.
>> Yes.
>> Michael, are you sharing right now?
>> Yes. Do you see me?
>> Yeah.
>> Your your three instances, knock them
out. Delete them. We don't need them.
>> So, stop stop stop. Go to the top and
select all of them. So, let's go next to
status. Yeah. Click there and then say
stop.
Say more actions.
Delete.
Yep, there you go. Okay, now go to
instance template.
Wait, back up real quick. I think he
went straight to creating the instance
on the left hand side.
I guess you could do it that way too.
Click on instance templates.
Create
instance template.
Name your instance template.
Um, wait, go back up.
Just as a suggestion, if you're going to
be using any of the particular scripts
that are showing up in um in Theo's
repo, I would recommend just naming it
here so when you go to use the template,
you know what it is. Otherwise, you have
to remember what Saturday 52261 is.
>> Okay, gotcha.
>> So, all right, you have basic open.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, we'll make basic.sh SH
or just take out the create and take out
thesh.
Just call it basic.
It has to start with a lower case. You
can't have uppercase in the name.
There we go. Okay. Scroll down.
Keep scrolling. Keep scrolling.
Dang, it's that far now. Stop. Allow
HTTP traffic.
Scroll some more. Click on advanced
options.
Scroll down under networking. Click on
networking real quick.
And Yep. So, the HTTP server tag is on
there. Cool. Um, then we're going to
management.
Scroll down.
So, where automation startup script is,
you're just going to copy the the script
from there and bring it over.
Scroll. Scroll. Scroll. Create.
So
just give us some time. There you go.
Template's created. So now if you want
to make an instance from it, you see the
three dots on the right hand under
actions.
>> Under actions on the right hand.
>> Yep. Yep. Click on those. You can create
a VM from that straight from there.
Click create VM.
It's going to have the name and
everything in there. Scroll, scroll,
scroll, scroll. It's going off of your
template. So, your templates fresh and
new. We know what we put in there, but
you can double check it as well. And
create.
All right. So now click on SSH.
I click on it.
>> Yes, sir.
There you go.
All right, you're good. You're in. You
can ping nike.com if you want or
something like that, but you're good.
Um, and then go back to the other page
for your external IP.
Go back to your console rather. Copy the
external IP. External. The one on the
right. Yeah, that one. and then new tab.
http colon forward forward.
Wait, you're good.
Was that so hard?
>> Not at all. No.
>> There you go.
Yeah, I think you guys did a good job.
That was That's pretty good. Nest egg,
put the bright hyperlink in there. You
don't just put an IP address in there.
Got to put the hyperlink in.
You already know this.
I was uh focus on the screen. Who who
who was helping me?
>> That was me.
>> Oh, appreciate this, man. Yes, sir.
>> Coach. Coach. All right.
Okay, there I go. Nest egg. Much better.
I like that. Okay, now the reason I'm
getting on you that day because we don't
want you to do that in the office. You
need to give something that's clickable.
If you do that in the office here, okay,
here they give it to you. They're gonna
say, "What the is this?" Right?
That's that's how a manager acts. I'll
make sure you get this right.
Uh, Michael, uh, that script takes a
while to load.
It's not immediate. So, a lot of these
scripts, remember I had you could SSH
first and then do the URL.
It's because it takes time for the
script to start up, right?
>> Okay. What we got here?
Heyo, can you hear me?
>> Yep, I can hear you.
>> Yeah. So, um, sorry to sidetrack the
class, but what I did was after class
yesterday, I spun up a VM. I put your
father 2 and I let the VM run like
literally all day. And then the next
day,
>> it still didn't run.
>> Yeah, it was still throwing that uh
default Debian uh screen.
>> I have to go look at it. Okay. Okay,
man. That's up. Okay, fine. I'll
go deal with that.
I got that uh pair. All right. You win
some, you lose some. All right. Fine.
Okay. Now, we need to use manage
instance groups or just make instance
group scripts. Is that well, it's kind
of managed. All right. So, why don't we
do a manage instance groups? Um the
reason why we're going to do manage
instance groups is because sometimes we
don't want to have just one uh VM
running. we want to have multiple VMs
running. Okay, this usually this is for
testing purposes. Um the reason why it's
going to be done is irrelevant to be
honest. It's just a requirement that
you'd have in the office. So a dev a guy
in dev might say look um I need to to
test my code. I need to have five
different VMs. Can you spin it up for me
and give me the access to it? That's it.
You spin it up, you give them the access
and he's like, "Okay, cool. I can go do
my work." All right. And then you be
like, "Yeah, I'm gonna check your H1B.
Deport your ass." All right.
Oh, I'm so bad today. Just bad. Stop,
Theo. Drink some coffee. All right. So,
anyway,
we're we're going to make manage
instance groups. Okay. Now, you're going
to understand why the template's
important.
Okay. So, who wants to show how to make
a managed instance group? Who else in
this?
>> I'll go.
Coach, I thought you guys would all be
jumping trying to do this.
Okay,
this is templates.
We're talking about your father's shoes
too. So,
we'll create instance group from
that template.
Instance name
big papa one just cuz why not? Instance
group rather. Instance template we're
using is big papa. Um are we doing it
with or without the autoscaling?
>> Uh let's do it without the autoscaling
this time. I I like
we'll do the autoscaling with the uh big
later on but for now yeah I I liked it
better without because it only spins one
in the end and I was kind like
let's do more that so yeah so how number
of instances let's put four on there
>> are you
>> I am indeed
>> okay
>> so we've got four
location zones make sure that we open up
all four available.
>> Okay. So, why do we do multiple zones
>> in case Iran targets Iowa and A is no
longer available?
>> That's correct. Yeah, that's right. So,
if again we have this situation in the
Middle East where Iran is targeting data
centers, right? And it took out like
part of one of uh uh AWS's AZ. Where was
it? I forgot what country it is. Um, and
the liberals are going on crazy about
this. Oh, and I started laughing. I was
like, well, if the designers did it
correct, they don't care if they lost
one a. It doesn't matter cuz it should
be in multiple AC, so it doesn't matter.
Go ahead and take one. We got three
others. All right. So, this is an
example. Um, your a when you do a
deployment like this with multiple VMs,
they should always be in multiple as.
That's just the way it is. Do not put
them all into one a. Uh, Everett, what
you got?
>> All right. So, he How did we already
have a instance script to call your
father, my father, whatever, whatever
it's called already in his drop down?
You know what I mean? Like, is that
something I need to be creating first?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Only follow
what he's doing.
>> So, I don't need to be doing it. Just
watch what he's doing.
>> Okay.
>> And follow along with what he's doing.
>> Well, that's what I'm saying. How can I
follow along if I don't already have
that created? I don't know.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. He's not dealing
with anything that's already created.
Nope. Nope. Nope, no, no. Um,
>> Theo, hold on, hold on. Theo, can you
clarify on what the it is that will be
utilized for the manage instance group?
>> Uh, it's a template. So, uh, coach,
coach to the top. What's the top
>> coach? So, for you did it.
>> So, you're talking about the manage
instance template, right?
>> Uh yeah, in the very beginning, I
thought he said uh he was going to use
like something called father or you
know, whatever. And all all I have is
the one that we just created.
>> Okay. So, why do you need more than one?
>> Well, I don't know asking about whether
he needs more than one. He's asking if
there's a difference between the naming
of what the coach did and what he has.
>> But ultimately, it's the core. It's the
same core. You need a template created.
>> Yeah.
>> In order to utilize the template for the
manage instance group. So if you have a
template, then you can actually move
forward.
>> That's it.
>> Okay.
>> Okay. Well, it's just because I already
created something with that template, so
I wasn't sure if there would be like
overlap and I needed to create another
one, but All right. So,
>> why would why would there be overlap?
>> Well, I didn't talk about overlap. A
template is a template.
>> Okay. All right. I just want to be
clear. So, all right. So, I'll do that.
>> That's what I thought too, Vanny.
Something like that. Um,
>> so can can you start over? uh socket.
>> Well, hold on. He's He hasn't done
anything yet. So, what he has there, do
something similar like there.
Okay. I'm just saying step by step. The
first thing I need to do is go to
instance template and then because I
don't even see a drop down. I'm just
seeing the instance templates. But I
think I should be seeing
>> in front of you. Select whatever
instance template that you have that you
want to use for this.
And then what I did is on the right hand
side you'll see the three vertical dots.
Click on those and you'll see an option
to create instance group from there.
>> Okay, great. All right. Now I'm on the
same page. All right.
>> You can name it whatever you want, guys.
Doesn't have to be this. Obviously, your
instance template's going to be
something different.
Um,
so multiple zones
D. We're not doing any autoscaling on
this one.
Auto healing. Health check.
Create a health check.
Health CCK. There we go.
That's what it is. We're making it
regional
and we want the logs on.
Health criteria check every 5 seconds.
Time outs for five. Healthy. Okay,
great. Save it.
And
what am I missing? Am I missing
anything?
Nope.
We'll create.
>> You did hell trick already?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Wow, that was fast. Damn.
Ahmad, you have a question.
>> It says Amod raised his hand. Amod, you
got a question?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm sorry. What was your uh
what was your uh settings for the health
chat?
Uh uh.
Hold on.
Can I pull him up from in here?
Where do we go?
So basically I named it.
I switched from global to regional
description was already in. And then the
only other thing I touched was the where
are we
logs enabled those.
That was good.
Okay. Yeah. Show the VMs. Wow. Look at
all the big popup.
Look at that.
>> Um,
but you were saying you were having
issues with your father, too. And that's
what Big Papa is,
>> so I test it.
>> I have I have problems with Big Papa.
I'm in therapy for that.
>> We're good.
>> Yeah, that's that's good, man. I like I
like how you did that. That was that was
very good.
Thank you sir. And I will stop sharing
my screen. Did anybody have any
questions?
>> Yeah, to be honest, I do. This is Ever.
Uh, so cuz I was looking, you know, at
the other screen and you were describing
certain things and then I just ended up
not so health check. I never really
heard about that. Then I then I know I
that's the first time I heard about
that. I was doing something different.
And then I heard you say about changing
the region, which I don't believe I did.
So I don't know if I'm if I'm on the
right if I've done it correctly or not,
you know, I mean,
>> all right, I'll I'll make it again. I'm
going to use the Super A template.
>> Well, this time have him share his
screen.
>> Yeah, deal. I'll share it right now. Oh,
give me one second.
place.
Um,
>> okay. So,
uh, All right. Can All right. Can you
see that?
>> Yes, I can. You're in instance group.
Okay. Go to your instance templates.
>> Okay. Well, here's instance group. See
instance
still compute.
Guess I got to get out
here at the very top. If you ever get
lost like this and you're looking for
something,
>> you see the search box in the middle
like that or X out of this
>> the search box right here. You can type
in
Uh yeah, type in instance templates
since that's what we're doing.
All right. And you see that second
there. Oh, the first one rather.
>> Click on it.
>> So this is the instance template that
you have. You see on the right hand side
of that uh of that row. Yep. Click on
actions or more actions
and create instance group.
>> Right now, now I guess you can see that
I did this part already, but so I don't
know if I need to erase what I've
already done.
>> Don't worry about it. We'll we'll delete
them after in the breakdown.
>> Um,
name whatever you want to name the
census group.
>> So change this name then, right? I'll
just do
>> Okay.
Okay, you've already got your instance
template. You see where it says number
of instances underneath the instance
template?
>> Yeah.
>> Change that to four.
>> And then scroll down under location.
>> All right. So, you've got multiple zones
selected. Click on the zones dropown box
and make sure that US Central 1A is
clicked.
Hit okay.
All right. Now, scroll down. Oh, hold.
So, stop. You see right right about
where your cursor is, if you go up one
box where it says health check.
>> Okay.
>> Click on that. Click on that.
>> You're going to create a health check.
>> Okay.
>> And you can name the health check
whatever you want to name it.
>> All right.
Uh,
okay.
>> All right. Under scope, click regional.
>> Uh, it doesn't like that.
>> Oh, sorry. You can't you can't have
capitalized.
>> Yeah, I just do that out of Okay.
>> Okay.
>> You're good there. And then under logs,
click on. So, let's scroll down a little
bit.
Logs on.
>> Yeah.
>> And then you got 5522. Hit save.
And you're good.
>> Okay. And this this always pops up here.
>> Yeah. It's nothing. So it it's what that
thing is telling you is when you start
when you create it and it launches
everything, it's going to look like the
world is burning for at least 10
seconds.
>> Okay.
All right. Uh All right.
>> Amongst other things, I click create at
the bottom bottom left.
>> Okay.
I think you count it out.
Oh, wow. My stuff is taking so long.
Maybe I have too much stuff.
>> No, don't worry. Don't worry. Be easy.
Be cool.
>> It's It's doing its thing.
>> All right.
>> It just turned blue. From blue, it'll
turn green. Just give it some time.
You can click on the instance name if
you want to look at, you know, what's
going on on the inside right now, but
you're good.
>> Okay.
Click on it now. Instance group 357.
Okay, you're good. It has the health
check on there. You've got your four
instances.
Give it a few more seconds. Still
updating
You know your health checks are working.
>> You say they are.
>> See, you've got three out of four going
right now on healthy
>> healthy status,
>> right?
>> It'll test again given the the um
>> what'll be put in there for settings,
but it should make a new one. There you
go. It'll make you a new one. And then
there you go. You've got them all 100%
healthy.
>> All right. Perfect.
>> What are you going to want a screenshot
of this page or? Well, I mean, obviously
you see maybe you don't need mine, but
um
>> I screenshot it before I leave from you.
Okay,
that's your proof that everything's
working the way it needs to.
Okay, you want me to stop sharing?
That's up to Theo.
>> That was pretty good. All right.
>> All right. Good deal. Thank you.
>> All right. Next person who hasn't done
managed groups.
>> Quick question.
>> Yep.
>> What's the reason we're doing this again
is for testing purposes. Let's say
someone wants to test their own codes
and this is
for testing purposes.
>> Why do we create groups? The real reason
why you're doing this is to understand
uh how to set up um scaling groups, ASGs
or MIGs.
So the rest of the students understand
that's what I'm actually doing right now
because they're in class 7 and earlier.
So they know I'm actually putting you
into a position to do this. That's all.
Um I'm not I tend not to do like
template and load balancer on the same
day because it can drive you crazy. So
I'm just doing template this week to
make sure you understand that you can
save the instructions of how to make a
instance in a template and then you can
use managed instances as well. But when
we go to load balancers
you're going to be doing like like you
can do 10 to 20 instances at one time.
>> Yeah.
>> You can do 400. You can do quite a a
number of these. So it's I'm just
setting you up for this. That's all.
Okay,
>> it's a reinforcement of uh following
instructions,
paying attention, stuff like that
because when a when we do full MIG, so
so unlike AWS, we can do
um
load balancing over regions very easily
with uh GCP.
Well, it's the other two clouds don't
have this capability. This is this is
actually phenomenal that GCP has. So I'm
going to be doing load balancing say
between like UK and Ohio or UK and Iowa
or something like that it'll be
something really cool. Um so if we don't
get this part done right now correctly
if you get confused with that other part
and then you have confusion with
instance template and that oh yeah yeah
you're dead. You won't you won't be able
to function. So, I'm making sure that
this is good in your brains first, then
we can go to the next part.
Um,
part of curriculum. So, don't sleep. Uh,
Christopher, what's up?
>> Hello, sir. Yesterday, uh, I followed
the instructions to a tea and my health
check didn't turn out well, but today I
followed the same thing and everything's
working. Um, I wanted to know what could
have been some of my area or something.
>> Some sometimes,
you know, you got prostate cancer.
Sometimes you got a happy pea park. You
know what I mean?
>> Okay.
>> You don't know what you got. I mean, it
could be one or the other. Uh, got to be
like, "All right.
>> All right.
>> Just play around with your health checks
and you'll be fine." Okay.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> What have I GOT OUT THERE?
I GOT PROSTATE CANCER. OH, SOLVE IT.
Every single blob must be impregnated.
Okay. I'm nuts. I'm having so much fun.
Anyway, okay. Who hasn't done this?
Who hasn't done it? Who didn't do manage
instance groups?
you all did it cuz if y'all if you
didn't do this that next week you will
be hating life. I guarantee you I'm
going to come into class and say look
Theo like what you just had us do I just
want you to know I hate you Theo like
that's what's going to be next week cuz
when we do front end backendm
front end backend is not a fun
configuration with GCP. It works well
but it's a to do. So I want to
make sure you guys got this part done.
We all good? All right, that's all you
got this week. All right. Um, I'm going
to get I'm going to sign you some
homework. It's going to be for from
Udemi. All right. If you haven't
submitted homework, submit homework.
Okay.
Um, I think you guys are doing well so
far. Okay. Talk with your group. If
you've got questions, communicate that
within your group or go to the main chat
and ask what your questions are.
Actually, say something. Okay. Yep. Uh,
TIQS's group submit
or you know what's happening. You know,
TIQS has a katana.
You know, you can see what's up. You
know what's going on.
Yeah, Michael. That's what
Yeah, Michael. That is how like f I'm
pretty sure father your father too is
supposed to look like that. Something
like that.
I was trying to get a Darth Vader um
mask to appear in Asi. That was my whole
goal.
I was trying to do something cool like
that. It didn't exactly work, but I mean
I I that's what I was trying to do.
Okay guys, uh see you next week and good
job. I think you guys are doing well.
Talk to you later. Johnny,
>> don't forget